Sorry for calling you out of the blue. I've been thinking about you and making gummy bears.
Here you go.
Ah.
Just kidding.
Nighttime and idols.
So, the second element that makes you Mr. Kokubou is a game.
Yes, games.
You like games?
Yes, I do.
I used to live in Aichi Prefecture and moved to Tokyo,
I've been gradually improving my gaming environment,
What is it? Gaming environment?
I started to get a gaming desk, a gaming chair, monitors, and so on,
It's a world you've always dreamed of, isn't it?
That's right.
It's a game room.
It's a really nice space. Is it a great space right now?
It's pretty close to my ideal. Gaming rooms are shiny, aren't they?
That's why I'm thinking of buying a new one.
Wait a minute, I don't know that much about it. Do gaming rooms look shiny?
But do you have an image of shiny gaming PCs?
Blue, for example. They're all shiny in different colors, so there are a lot of things that are shiny.
I don't really know what they are shiny for. Yes, it is. Maybe they are shiny for the purpose of making a video.
Is it for the video? It's a reflection.
Wow. Do you stream videos?
I've done a video distribution...
I did a game stream once with just sound. Just sound?
I turned the volume down and played the game with just sound. I see.
What games do you recommend? What are you into now?
Games you're addicted to? I've always been addicted to Apex.
Uh, together? Yes, we are.
But I don't have many friends in Tokyo anymore. So I play games alone.
Were there a lot of other local gamers who played the same game?
Yes, I did. But in StarPlaza, I play games with Kaaya-chan.
I see. Together? We play Apex together.
You play at the same time. Yes, we do.
Yes, we do. The games are pretty good, too. What do you enjoy most?
What do you enjoy most? I really enjoy winning. It's fun to win.
It's a shooting game, so I'm happy just to hit the target.
It's fun to find an enemy and hit him while avoiding him.
It's really fun to try to find the enemy and hit them while avoiding hitting them.
If there are fans of Ebichu, they might be fighting, too.
I'm sure they are fighting.
That's right.
They're probably doing it in the world of Apex.
They're probably doing it.
Do you ever have conversations with people like, "Hey, does this person know about Elch?
No, not yet. I don't get into that kind of conversation.
I don't talk about my private life with anyone.
But I really don't know.
There's also voice chat, but I'm not going to do that.
You don't do voice chat?
I thought it might be dangerous.
That's right.
But the other day, a total stranger turned on voice chat by mistake.
He was singing the whole time.
That's nice.
He seemed to be having a lot of fun.
I was playing the game while listening to him.
I was playing the game while listening to the voice of the person who forgot to listen to the office chat.
He was singing while everyone was fighting.
Yes, with a little background music.
Really?
Yes, sir.
How many hours a day do you play?
When I'm at home all day long...
I do it from the time I wake up in the morning until I go to bed at night.
That's amazing.
That's real.
Yes, it is.
Excuse me.
How long are the fights?
Well, it really depends on how strong the enemy is.
It's not over until you're down to your last man.
The last one?
Yes, sir.
And that's why some fights last longer than 40 minutes.
Over 40 minutes?
That's great.
Let's see what you got.
I'd love to do that.
I really want to do game distribution.
You know... game distribution.
That's right.
I'd love to.
Does your personality change a lot? When you play games...
I don't know.
When I'm playing with my friends.
I might change.
Really?
On the contrary.
It's a little more exciting.
As a viewer.
I'm looking forward to seeing more of that in the future, and I'd like to see it.
The second element of Kukuma's work is that it's a game.
We've already finished Soratonaru, haven't we?
Yes, we've already done that.
What are some of the challenges you've taken on recently?
This program, Mizuna,
Ms. Nagi,Nagi-san,
Mr. Sakana-hanato,
Soo-san,
We sent you many offers.
Thank you very much.